<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<hotspots>
	<hotspot>
		<name> Sky </name>
		<positionX> 1400  </positionX>
		<positionY> 100 </positionY>
		<description> The sky is the part of the atmosphere or outer space visible from the surface of any astronomical object. It is difficult to define precisely for several reasons. During daylight, the sky of Earth has the appearance of a pale blue surface because of the air's scattering of sunlight.[1][2][3][4] The sky is sometimes defined as the denser gaseous zone of a planet's atmosphere. At night the sky has the appearance of a black surface or region scattered with stars.
				During the day the Sun can be seen in the sky, unless obscured by clouds. In the night sky (and to some extent during the day) the moon, planets and stars are visible in the sky. Some of the natural phenomena seen in the sky are clouds, rainbows, and aurorae. Lightning and precipitation can also be seen in the sky during storms. On Earth, birds, insects, aircraft, and kites are often considered to fly in the sky. As a result of human activities, smog during the day and light radiance during the night are often seen above large cities (see also light pollution). </description>
	<hotspot>
	
	<hotspot>
		<name> Sea </name>
		<positionX> 1400 </positionX>
		<positionY> 850 </positionY>
		<description> A sea generally refers to a large body of salt water, but the term is used in other contexts as well. Most commonly, the term refers to a large expanse of saline water connected with an ocean, and is commonly used as a synonym for ocean.[1] It is also used sometimes to describe a large saline lake that lacks a natural outlet, such as the Caspian Sea.</description>
	<hotspot>
	
	<hotspot>
		<name> Men </name>
		<positionX> 1000 </positionX>
		<positionY> 750 </positionY>
		<description> Humans, known taxonomically as Homo sapiens[3][4] (Latin for "wise man" or "knowing man"),[5] are the only living species in the Homo genus of bipedal primates in Hominidae, the great ape family. Anatomically modern-appearing humans originated in Africa about 200,000 years ago, reaching full behavioral modernity around 50,000 years ago. </description>
	<hotspot>
	
		<hotspot>
		<name> Land </name>
		<positionX> 1600 </positionX>
		<positionY> 950 </positionY>
		<description> Land may refer to: The part of the Earth that is not covered by water. Terrestrial ecoregion, an ecoregion based on soil instead of water
</description>
	<hotspot>
</hotspots> 